The huge advanced topics, we are going to see with some of the easiest way to turn off
the defender that was running in the local machine.
So, here you can find a small back file, so you can download it from, you will get easily
if you search for disabled windows defenders or that, okay, ended up.
So, here you can find some of the rich commands to add two modified few of the registry
key that was responsible for windows defender, if you can download this way and extract
here, okay, find where this, you put it in this directory, extract here, so now we have
a directory and the disabled defender, just run as administrator, so it will turn off each
and every, it will turn off all the entire software, it is different, okay, not on any
software, it is completely a local machine, windows defender, so this one of the easiest
way to quickly disable the service through deleting the deleting or modifying few of the registry
and schedule task and services.
So I hope you have a clear understanding about this one, this one has a pretty easy to, things
to do and just execute the back file in the target machine, so what you, which you have
compromised, yeah, that's all about this one, we will jump on to the next video, see you
bye bye.